idIdioma;idPergunta;Nivel;Competencia;Pergunta
2;1;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the sentence: "My family __________ very big."
2;2;Básico;Verb to be;Choose the correct alternative: "Nathalie __________ sick today."
2;3;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the sentence with the correct alternative: "Okay, you are right. I __________ sorry."
2;4;Básico;Verb to be;Choose the correct alternative: "They __________ all very good friends."
2;5;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the sentence: "Today __________ the 19th of January."
2;6;Básico;Verb to be;What is the correct alternative? "I _________ a software developer."
2;7;Básico;Verb to be;Choose the correct form: "She __________ here right now. May I take a message?"
2;8;Básico;Verb to be;Choose the correct alternative: "__________ she his boss?"
2;9;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the sentence: "Adolescents __________ usually very active."
2;10;Básico;Verb to be;Which of the following alternatives is incorrect? "I _________a lawyer."
2;11;Básico;Verb to be;Choose the correct alternative: "My father __________ in the kitchen."
2;12;Básico;Verb to be;Choose the correct answer: "The pupils __________ at school today."
2;13;Básico;Verb to be;Choose the correct alternative: "It __________ Sunday today."
2;14;Básico;Verb to be;Choose the correct answer: "__________ careful! It is hot!"
2;15;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the sentence: "__________ you from Scotland?"
2;16;Básico;Verb to be;Choose the incorrect alternative: "His sister __________ seven years old."
2;17;Básico;Verb to be;Choose the incorrect alternative: "We __________ children."
2;18;Básico;Verb to be;Choose the best answer: "My grandmother's name __________ Adelaide."
2;19;Básico;Verb to be;Which of the following is verb to be?
2;20;Básico;Verb to be;Which of the following is not verb to be?
2;21;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the sentence with the correct alternatives: "__________ ready for your holidays, Lucy? Yes, __________!"
2;22;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the sentence: "__________ excited about this trip, it's going to be __________!"
2;23;Básico;Verb to be;Choose the correct alternative: "Where _______________ from?"
2;24;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the sentence: "The food there __________ really good but the waiters __________ quite rude."
2;25;Básico;Verb to be;Choose the correct alternative:xptoBryan: "__________ Zurich the capital of Switzerland?"xptoLucy: "No, __________ Bern."
2;26;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the sentence: "I think __________ a bus driver."
2;27;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the sentence: "This is Ana. __________ my friend."
2;28;Básico;Verb to be;Choose the correct answer: "I'm from a city called Turin. __________ in Italy."
2;29;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the sentence: "I'm Cary and this is Thomas. _______________ architects."
2;30;Básico;Verb to be;Choose the correct alternative:           xptoMike: "Is she your mom?" xptoSarah: "_______________."                                
2;31;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the sentence: "Billy __________ from the United States."
2;32;Básico;Verb to be;Choose the correct alternative: "Nice car. _______________ yours?"
2;33;Básico;Verb to be;Choose the correct answer: "I __________ thirty-one years old."
2;34;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the sentence: "_______________ happy?"
2;35;Básico;Verb to be;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ coming to the party?"
2;36;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the sentence: "Anna _______________ at home at the moment. Please come back later."
2;37;Básico;Verb to be;Choose the correct alternative: xptoCary: "Where's John?" xptoJames: "_______________ at work."
2;38;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the sentence: "My cousins __________ going downtown tomorrow."
2;39;Básico;Verb to be;Choose the correct alternative: "My sister __________ not a child anymore."
2;40;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the sentence: xptoAnna: "Are you and Mark cousins?"xptoStella: "No, we __________."
2;41;Básico;Verb to be;Choose the correct answer: xptoMark: "__________ this your seat?"xptoPeter: "Yes, it __________."
2;42;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the sentence: "We __________ Brazilian. We are not Portuguese."
2;43;Básico;Verb to be;Choose the correct alternative: xptoAimee: "Are you an engineer?"xptoPaul: "Yes, I __________."
2;44;Básico;Verb to be;Choose the correct answer:xptoLisa: "Is your room number 12?"xptoMick: "No, it __________. It's number 15."
2;45;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the sentence: "__________ Lulu a dog?"
2;46;Básico;Verb to be;Choose the correct alternative: "My dad __________ an astronaut. He's a dentist."
2;47;Básico;Verb to be;Choose the correct answer: "__________ you cold?"
2;48;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the question: "_______________ tall enough to play on the basketball team?"
2;49;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the dialogue:xptoCarl: "_______________ in South America?"xptoBruce: "Yes, _______________."
2;50;Básico;Verb to be;Choose the correct alternative: xptoAnn: "Where __________ Tim and Sue?"xptoMark: "They __________ at school."
2;51;Básico;Verb to be;Choose the correct answer: "The teachers always says good things about my son. He __________ a very good student."
2;52;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the sentence: "The weather is nice today. It __________ raining."
2;53;Básico;Verb to be;Choose the correct alternative: "It __________ 10 o'clock! You __________ going to be late for school!"
2;54;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the dialogue: xptoSally: "__________ John rich?"xptoBob: "Yes, he __________ very rich."
2;55;Básico;Verb to be;Choose the correct answer: "Don't come in! Your shoes __________ very dirty!"
2;56;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the sentence: "Can you help me, please? This bag __________ very heavy."
2;57;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the dialogue:xptoSue: "Where __________ Aimee's car?"xptoPeter: "It __________ in the garage."
2;58;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the dialogue:xptoMark: "__________ your mom retired?"xptoSarah: "No, she __________."
2;59;Básico;Verb to be;Choose the correct answer: "Take my car. They keys __________ on the table."
2;60;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the sentence: "Your watch __________ really beautiful. I loved it."
2;61;Básico;Verb to be;Choose the best answer: "My friend and I __________ dentists. __________ aren't psychologists."
2;62;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the sentence: "The Leaning Tower of Pisa is in Italy. _______________ in France."
2;63;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the sentence: "How old _______________? _______________ young?"
2;64;Básico;Verb to be;Choose the correct alternative: "My neighbor's children __________ very disobedient. They never listen to their parents."
2;65;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the sentence: "Hello, nice to meet you. These __________ my business partners, James and Alice."
2;66;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the sentence: "My parents love Italian food. Their favorite food __________ ravioli."
2;67;Básico;Verb to be;Choose the correct alternative: "Today __________ Thursday, _______________ Friday."
2;68;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the sentence: "Thomas and I __________ very good friends. I like him."
2;69;Básico;Verb to be;Choose the correct alternative: "Paul and Tracy __________ always late for class."
2;70;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the sentence: "_______________ raining today. Let's go to the beach."
2;71;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the dialogue:xptoWaiter: "Good morning sir, __________ ready to order your food?"xptoWilliam: "Yes, __________, thank you."
2;72;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the sentence: "_______________ time to make some changes in our company."
2;73;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the sentence: "I like this restaurant. Their prices __________ high but the food __________  very good."
2;74;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the sentence: "Martha and her friends __________ very good architects. Look at their last project, it's wonderful!"
2;75;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the sentence: "Copenhagen __________ the capital of Denmark."
2;76;Básico;Verb to be;Choose the correct alternative: "Niko and Sofia __________ from Greece." 
2;77;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the sentence: "My teacher __________ a very intelligent person. I'm proud of her. "
2;78;Básico;Verb to be;Choose the correct alternative: "My neighbors have a beautiful son. _______________ 2 years old."
2;79;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the sentence: "__________ your friends interested in art?"
2;80;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the sentence: "My husband __________ an engineer, _______________ a software developer."
2;81;Básico;Verb to be;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ too difficult to learn Chinese?"
2;82;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the sentence: "Pamela and Bryan __________ very good friends. They see each other almost every day."
2;83;Básico;Verb to be;Choose the correct alternative: "Both my parents __________ brown eyes, but I __________ blue eyes."
2;84;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the dialogue: xptoNancy: "What _______________?"xptoBryan: "It __________ a bicycle tool."
2;85;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the question: "_______________ inside or outside the house?"
2;86;Básico;Verb to be;Choose the correct answer: "You don't need a jacket. It __________ cold. It's hot."
2;87;Básico;Verb to be;Choose the correct alternative: "Jennifer and Tom __________ at the cinema. They're at the park."
2;88;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the sentence: "My mother __________ a doctor. She's an architect."
2;89;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the question: "Dinner is ready. __________ you hungry?"
2;90;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the dialogue:xptoPaul: "__________ the children home?"xptoJess: "No, they __________."
2;91;Básico;Verb to be;Choose the correct answer: "Ted and Sam study a lot. They __________ very good students."
2;92;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the dialogue:xptoSam: "__________ Pat and Kelly on vacation?"xptoJohn: "Yes, they __________."
2;93;Básico;Verb to be;Choose the correct alternative: "Shhh! Be quiet! We __________ at a library!"
2;94;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the sentence: "This __________ the magazine I love reading."
2;95;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the question: "__________ that your neighbor?"
2;96;Básico;Verb to be;Choose the correct answer: "My English classes __________ so much fun! I love them!"
2;97;Básico;Verb to be;Choose the correct alternative: "My children's teacher __________ very funny! They love her!"
2;98;Básico;Verb to be;Complete the sentence: "John __________ at home and the children __________ playing outside."
2;99;Básico;Verb to be;Choose the correct answer: "Your garden __________ beautiful! It's so colorful!"
2;100;Básico;Verb to be;Choose the correct alternative: "My parents ___________ in Italy. They __________ in Venice."
2;101;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Complete the sentence: "Wow, __________ pancakes taste really good!"
2;102;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct answer: "My brother is a soccer player. __________ name is Romário."
2;103;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;What is the correct alternative?: "I have a female dog. __________ name is Lola."
2;104;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct answer: "I love Paris and __________ museums."
2;105;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct alternative: "Hi, __________ name is Sally."
2;106;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Complete the sentence: xptoPaula: "What's __________ name?"xptoJosh: "__________ name's Edward."
2;107;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Complete the sentence: "These are my daughters. __________ names are Samantha and Alice."
2;108;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Complete the sentence. "This is my mother. __________ name is Sandra."
2;109;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct alternative: "My brother is funny. __________ jokes are the best."
2;110;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Complete the sentence: "I'm 20 today. It's __________ birthday."
2;111;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct answer: "My dad is a writer. This is __________ computer." 
2;112;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct alternative: "I liked Anna. Could you give me __________ phone number?"
2;113;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct answer: "They are brothers. __________ names are Brian and Thomas."
2;114;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Complete the sentence: "This is my dog. __________ name is Rufus."
2;115;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct alternative: xptoSarah: "Do you like my hair?"xptoPaty: "Yes, I really like __________ hair."
2;116;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct answer: "My sister is beautiful. __________ eyes are dark brown."
2;117;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Complete the sentence: "Pete brushes __________ teeth three times a day."
2;118;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct alternative:xptoKelly: "Where's Kate?"xptoJohn: "She's in __________ room."
2;119;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct answer: "Ann and Tom are happy. __________ children are back home!"
2;120;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Complete the sentence: "__________ look pretty today. __________ dress is beautiful!"
2;121;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct alternative: "Julie is a girl and __________ surname is Jackson."
2;122;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct answer: "My dog's name is Fred. __________ ears are brown."
2;123;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Complete the sentence: "I'm a doctor and __________ favorite TV show is 'Grey's Anatomy'."
2;124;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct alternative: "It's raining and you didn't bring __________ umbrella with you."
2;125;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct answer: "Use these coloring pencils. I like __________ colors."
2;126;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Complete the sentence: "The boy is crying because __________ toy car is broken."
2;127;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Complete the dialogue:xptoKatie: "Why are you sad?"xptoPaul: "Because I lost __________ cell phone."
2;128;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct alternative: "Peter isn't Santa Claus but __________ beard is also white."
2;129;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct answer: "Raquel is Spanish but __________ mother is Brazilian."
2;130;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Complete the sentence: "That dog is mine. __________ name is Lilly."
2;131;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Complete the sentence: "Some people just don't worry about __________ health."
2;132;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct answer: "This is Mariana. __________ brother's name is Andrew."
2;133;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct answer: "These are my English teachers. __________ names are Martha and Peter."
2;134;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Complete the sentence: "My husband and I love sports. __________ favorites are surfing and cycling."
2;135;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct alternative: "Sophie and Lucas love __________ dog Rufo."
2;136;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Complete the sentence: "I love New York and __________ nice restaurants."
2;137;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct alternative: "Mary and Sally are American but __________ family is Canadian."
2;138;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Complete the sentence: "I love romantic authors. Do you like __________ novels?"
2;139;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Complete the sentence: "Peter doesn't have any money.  He lost __________ job last year."
2;140;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct alternative: "Do you have Jane's address? I can't find __________ house."
2;141;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Complete the sentence: "Mary and Tom like reading. __________ home library is really big."
2;142;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct alternative: "Josh is really messy. He always leaves __________ dirty clothes on the floor."
2;143;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Complete the sentence: "Hi Rita, what are __________ plans for today? What do you want to do?"
2;144;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct alternative:  "I can't stand my sister. She always borrows __________ clothes without asking me."
2;145;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Complete the sentence: "Janet has never seen snow in __________ life."
2;146;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;What is the correct alternative? "Honey, what do you think of buying a new wardrobe to __________ bedroom?"
2;147;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Complete the sentence: "They had dinner, and then he and __________ wife put their kids to bed."
2;148;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct alternative: "My father is Spanish. __________ name is Juan."
2;149;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct answer: "My school is very modern. __________ rooms are large and well equipped."
2;150;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct alternative: "These are Mr. and Mrs. Moran and __________ children."
2;151;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct answer: "I have two sisters. __________ names are Cindy and Anna."
2;152;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct answer: "We are very late. __________ classes begin at 8.30 a.m."
2;153;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct alternative: "My friend Alice is very happy. It is __________ birthday today."
2;154;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Complete the sentence: "Tom is really excited. It is __________ graduation party today."
2;155;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Complete the sentence: "__________ mother is looking for you. She thinks _______________ in school."
2;156;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Complete the sentence: "Call me tomorrow. Do you have __________ phone number?"
2;157;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct alternative: "Douglas is very disorganized. __________ room is a mess."
2;158;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Complete the sentence: "My friends and I love movies. __________ favorite kind is comedy."
2;159;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct alternative: "I have a dog and a cat. __________ names are Francis and Renée."
2;160;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Complete the sentence: "Amsterdam is famous for __________ canals."
2;161;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Complete the sentence: "_______________ my sisters Alice and Giovanna."
2;162;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct alternative: "I have three brothers. __________ names are John, Peter and Tim."
2;163;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct answer: "Tom and __________ sister are doctors."
2;164;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Complete the sentence: "We brought __________ own food and drinks." 
2;165;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Complete the question: "Do you have __________ books with you? You are going to need them."
2;166;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct answer: "The children are doing __________ homework in the bedroom."
2;167;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct alternative: "I can't find __________ pencil. Did you see it?"
2;168;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Complete the sentence: "This is a wonderful city. __________ sky is blue and clear."
2;169;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Complete the question: "Do you know where __________ bag is?"
2;170;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct answer: "These are Mr. and Mrs. Johnson and __________ children."
2;171;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct alternative: "His pet is a brown dog. __________ name is Jimmy."
2;172;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Complete the sentence: "Jess and Julie are very good students. __________ teachers are very happy with them."
2;173;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Complete the question: "Do __________ children like reading books?"
2;174;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct answer: "I have a girlfriend. __________ eyes are blue and her hair is blonde."
2;175;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct alternative: "My daughter loves blue. It's __________ favorite color."
2;176;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Complete the sentence: "My son doesn't like playing soccer. __________ favorite sport is basketball."
2;177;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Complete the question: "Peter likes reading books. Do you know who __________ favorite author is?"
2;178;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct answer: "Sarah loves watching movies. __________ favorite movie director is Quentin Tarantino."
2;179;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct alternative: "Mike and I bought a new house last year. __________ new house has a big garden."
2;180;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Complete the sentence: "Matt has a new laptop computer. __________ old computer broke down two months ago."
2;181;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Complete the question: "Whose books are __________ in my hands?"
2;182;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct answer: "I'm wearing my favorite red jacket. I bought __________ jacket last year."
2;183;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct alternative: "I love __________ shoes I'm wearing today."
2;184;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Complete the sentence: "Sarah is outside speaking with her friends. I don't really like __________ pants she is wearing today."
2;185;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Complete the question: "How much is __________ pair of socks I have in my hands?"
2;186;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct answer: "You have to take the bus and return the book to __________ public library downtown."
2;187;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct alternative: "I really like __________ coffee shop downtown. Let's go there!"
2;188;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Complete the sentence: "I always remember my trip to Italy and __________ wonderful restaurants."
2;189;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Complete the question: "Do you remember __________ books I lent you last year? I need them back."
2;190;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct answer: "I love remembering my childhood. __________ were happy days!"
2;191;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct alternative: "I really like __________ dress you are wearing today. It's so elegant!"
2;192;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Complete the sentence: "Let's go downtown and have dinner at __________ restaurant we love!"
2;193;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Complete the question: "I can't forget __________ things you told me yesterday."
2;194;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct answer: "Do you remember __________ song the band played yesterday?"
2;195;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct alternative: "__________ books in my hands are mine and __________ on the table are yours."
2;196;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Complete the sentence: "We can take the train and visit __________ old church downtown."
2;197;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Complete the question: "Where's __________ blue sweater I love so much?"
2;198;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct answer: "__________ children across the street are very happy playing outside."
2;199;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Choose the correct alternative: "__________ woman across the street is very beautiful."
2;200;Básico;Possessive adjectives and demonstrative pronouns;Complete the sentence: "__________ shops downtown are very expensive. I don't want to go there."
2;201;Básico;Present Simple;Complete the question: "Why _______________ so sad? What happened to her?"
2;202;Básico;Present Simple;Choose the correct alternative: "Come on, hurry up! The bus __________ at 5 o'clock!"
2;203;Básico;Present Simple;Complete the question: "__________ you __________ a smartphone?"
2;204;Básico;Present Simple;Complete the sentence: "My brother _______________ sweets, but he _______________ chocolate."
2;205;Básico;Present Simple;Choose the correct alternative: "There's no need to hurry. The party __________ at 9:00 p.m."
2;206;Básico;Present Simple;Complete the question: "What time __________ the pizza restaurant __________ on Sundays?"
2;207;Básico;Present Simple;Complete the question: "Jimmy has a strong accent. Where __________ he __________ from?"
2;208;Básico;Present Simple;Choose the correct alternative: "This is the first time that I __________ to this park."
2;209;Básico;Present Simple;Complete the sentence: "The sun __________ in the East."
2;210;Básico;Present Simple;Complete the sentence: "She __________ English very well but she is shy."
2;211;Básico;Present Simple;Choose the correct answer: "I usually __________ the news in the morning."
2;212;Básico;Present Simple;Complete the sentence: "She is a very dedicated musician. She __________ the piano every day."
2;213;Básico;Present Simple;Complete the sentence: "They __________ with their children almost every summer."
2;214;Básico;Present Simple;Choose the correct alternative: "He still needs to __________ the house before his guests arrive."
2;215;Básico;Present Simple;Complete the sentence: "My grandmother _______________ to fly because she gets nervous on the plane."
2;216;Básico;Present Simple;Choose the correct alternative: "Sarah __________ to relax when she __________ home from work."
2;217;Básico;Present Simple;Choose the best option: "Don't forget to __________ your seat on the plane."
2;218;Básico;Present Simple;Complete the sentence: "Mary and Bob __________ a son and a daughter."
2;219;Básico;Present Simple;Complete the sentence: "He wants to __________ the city, and his wife __________ to go to the modern art museum."
2;220;Básico;Present Simple;Choose the correct alternative: "Lana and her family __________ to the countryside every weekend."
2;221;Básico;Present Simple;Complete the sentence: "Plants __________ water to grow."
2;222;Básico;Present Simple;Choose the correct alternative: "My grandma __________ very well. I __________ her food."
2;223;Básico;Present Simple;Complete the sentence: "Robert always __________ what he __________ to do. He is very responsible."
2;224;Básico;Present Simple;Choose the correct alternative: "My brother and I __________ an apartment in New York."
2;225;Básico;Present Simple;Complete the sentence: "My friend _______________ to live here. He prefers big cities."
2;226;Básico;Present Simple;Choose the correct alternative: "My neighbor __________ his car every Sunday."
2;227;Básico;Present Simple;Choose the correct alternative: "__________ studies English every Tuesday and Thursday."
2;228;Básico;Present Simple;Complete the sentence: "_______________ work for an oil company."
2;229;Básico;Present Simple;Complete the sentence: "I like to __________ guava for breakfast. It __________ good."
2;230;Básico;Present Simple;Choose the correct alternative: "Sorry, I will be late because my car __________ a flat tire."
2;231;Básico;Present Simple;Complete the question: "How many brothers and sisters __________ Sarah __________?"
2;232;Básico;Present Simple;Choose the correct alternative: "You should always __________ healthy food."
2;233;Básico;Present Simple;Complete the sentence: "Paul and Cassia __________ a very nice and expensive car."
2;234;Básico;Present Simple;Choose the correct alternative: "This is the first time Mario and Alice _______________ by plane."
2;235;Básico;Present Simple;Complete the dialogue: xptoBryan: "What does _______________?"xptoLindsey: "She __________ books in a bookshop."
2;236;Básico;Present Simple;Choose the correct alternative: "My friend usually _______________ at 5:30 a.m. on working days."
2;237;Básico;Present Simple;Complete the sentence: "I now __________ a new job at the local school."
2;238;Básico;Present Simple;Complete the question: "Hi Laura, _______________ with us to the Japanese restaurant?"
2;239;Básico;Present Simple;Complete the sentence: "Sometimes it __________ in New York, so take your boots with you."
2;240;Básico;Present Simple;Choose the correct alternative: "My brother __________ his apartment."
2;241;Básico;Present Simple;What is the correct alternative?: "I_______________ Mary's husband. Is he nice?"
2;242;Básico;Present Simple;Complete the sentence: "Every morning, that awful noise __________ me up. I can't stand it anymore!"
2;243;Básico;Present Simple;Complete the sentence with the correct alternative: "The food in that restaurant __________ too salty."
2;244;Básico;Present Simple;Complete the question: "Does he usually __________ to work on time?"
2;245;Básico;Present Simple;Choose the correct alternative: "She __________ like sugar in her coffee."
2;246;Básico;Present Simple;Complete the sentence: "They __________ to the countryside every weekend."
2;247;Básico;Present Simple;Choose the correct alternative: "I __________ yoga twice a week. On Tuesdays and Thursdays."
2;248;Básico;Present Simple;Complete the sentence: "Does he __________ actively in the meetings?"
2;249;Básico;Present Simple;Choose the incorrect alternative: "The Fitzgeralds __________ to the seaside every summer."
2;250;Básico;Present Simple;Choose the correct answer: "I _________ understand the word 'rooster'. What __________ it mean?"
2;251;Básico;Present Simple;Choose the correct alternative: "British people __________ tea at 5 o'clock."
2;252;Básico;Present Simple;Choose the correct alternative: "My son __________ work."
2;253;Básico;Present Simple;Choose the incorrect answer: "She __________ swimming at night."
2;254;Básico;Present Simple;Choose the correct alternative: "Peter __________ breakfast at home."
2;255;Básico;Present Simple;Choose the best answer: "__________ Ann live in China?"
2;256;Básico;Present Simple;Choose the best alternative: "__________ Charlie and Sean play soccer on Fridays?"
2;257;Básico;Present Simple;Choose  the correct alternative: "__________ Patrick usually arrive on time?"
2;258;Básico;Present Simple;Choose the correct answer: "They __________ like seafood."
2;259;Básico;Present Simple;Complete the sentence: "My sister and her boyfriend __________ volleyball very well."
2;260;Básico;Present Simple;Choose the correct alternative: "Do you want to go to the park or __________ a movie?"
2;261;Básico;Present Simple;Complete the sentence: "My friend __________ in France."
2;262;Básico;Present Simple;Choose the correct alternative: "Melissa _______________ romantic movies."
2;263;Básico;Present Simple;Complete the sentence: "Clarice _______________ meat. She's a vegetarian."
2;264;Básico;Present Simple;Complete the sentence: "He's very sad right now. He _______________ to talk about it."
2;265;Básico;Present Simple;Choose the correct alternative: "My sister __________ to work."
2;266;Básico;Present Simple;Complete the sentence: "I _______________ live far from here."
2;267;Básico;Present Simple;Choose the correct answer: "They usually __________ dinner at 8 p.m."
2;268;Básico;Present Simple;Complete the sentence: "She __________ living in a warm country."
2;269;Básico;Present Simple;Complete the sentence: "We _______________ Chinese food, but we _______________ Japanese food." 
2;270;Básico;Present Simple;Choose the correct alternative: "My cooking class _______________ at 8:00."
2;271;Básico;Present Simple;Complete the sentence: "My husband and I _______________ a very good relationship."
2;272;Básico;Present Simple;Choose the correct alternative: "I _______________ to go to the party tonight. I want to go home."
2;273;Básico;Present Simple;Complete the sentence: "My son __________ to know that studying is a good thing for him." 
2;274;Básico;Present Simple;Complete the sentence: "We _______________ a computer at home."
2;275;Básico;Present Simple;Choose the correct alternative: "This train __________ downtown."
2;276;Básico;Present Simple;Complete the sentence: "Every work day, I __________ almost two hours in traffic."
2;277;Básico;Present Simple;Choose the best alternative: "I really __________ to learn German before I go to Germany next year."
2;278;Básico;Present Simple;Complete the sentence: "It's dangerous __________ when you're sleepy."
2;279;Básico;Present Simple;Choose the correct alternative: "What time __________ the movie start?"
2;280;Básico;Present Simple;Choose the correct answer: "Brian __________ soccer on Sundays."
2;281;Básico;Present Simple;Complete the sentence: "Sophie usually __________ on hot days."
2;282;Básico;Present Simple;Choose the correct alternative: "They __________ like going out at night."
2;283;Básico;Present Simple;Choose the correct answer:xptoTed: "__________ you like fishing?"xptoBill: "No, I don't."
2;284;Básico;Present Simple;Complete the sentence: "Sarah is very popular. She __________ many friends."
2;285;Básico;Present Simple;Choose the correct alternative: "They __________ their bedroom every weekend."
2;286;Básico;Present Simple;Choose the correct answer: "She __________ study on weekends".
2;287;Básico;Present Simple;Complete the sentence:xptoLilly: "Brian and Julie are coming for dinner tonight."xptoAnn: "__________ they eat seafood?"
2;288;Básico;Present Simple;Complete the sentence: "James __________ his bike to school every day. He loves it!"
2;289;Básico;Present Simple;Choose the correct answer: "Jennifer __________ reading. She __________ books every day."
2;290;Básico;Present Simple;Complete the sentence: "My children __________ to school by minibus."
2;291;Básico;Present Simple;Choose the correct alternative: "After school, Mike also __________ a lot at home."
2;292;Básico;Present Simple;Complete the dialogue: xptoSue: "__________ Eli __________ at home?"xptoSally: "No, he doesn't."
2;293;Básico;Present Simple;Choose the correct answer: "He __________ two languages: English and French."
2;294;Básico;Present Simple;Choose the correct alternative: "We __________ good films on TV every day."
2;295;Básico;Present Simple;Complete the sentence: "Ted _______________ computer games at home. I don't let him."
2;296;Básico;Present Simple;Complete the dialogue: xptoSam: "__________ Tina __________ the piano?"xptoSarah: "Yes, she plays it very well."
2;297;Básico;Present Simple;Choose the correct answer: "Even the best students __________ mistakes in the final exam."
2;298;Básico;Present Simple;Choose the correct answer: "My children never __________ late."
2;299;Básico;Present Simple;Choose the correct alternative: "Jennifer __________ riding horses on sunny days."
2;300;Básico;Present Simple;Complete the question: "__________ Jess __________ any children?"
2;301;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct answer: "I love working here. Everybody is very __________."
2;302;Básico;Adjectives;Complete the sentence: "My son is very __________. He never forgets to say 'please' and 'thank you'."
2;303;Básico;Adjectives;Complete the sentence: "The service in this hotel is __________. I will never come back here."
2;304;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct answer: "This book is very __________! I loved it!"
2;305;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct alternative: "I don't like this pair of pants. It's very __________."
2;306;Básico;Adjectives;Complete the sentence: "I really like this couch. It's very __________."
2;307;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct answer: "These exercises are very __________. I don't think I can do them."
2;308;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct alternative: "Your house is very __________. It's never dirty!"
2;309;Básico;Adjectives;Complete the sentence: "This room is very __________. Can we turn on the lights?"
2;310;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct answer: "He is very athletic and __________. I think I'm in love with him."
2;311;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct alternative: "These books are very __________. Can you help me, please?"
2;312;Básico;Adjectives;Complete the sentence: "This table is very __________. There isn't space for it in the living room."
2;313;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct answer: "Your hair is very __________. Why don't you cut it?"
2;314;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct alternative: "My son is not organized. His bedroom is always __________."
2;315;Básico;Adjectives;Complete the sentence: "My computer broke down yesterday. I need to buy a __________ one."
2;316;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct answer: "I like silence and spending time in __________ places."
2;317;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct alternative: "They have many properties and a lot of money. They are very __________."
2;318;Básico;Adjectives;Complete the sentence: "I can't cut the meat with this knife. It isn't __________!"
2;319;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct answer: "Turtles are __________, but they live a __________ time!"
2;320;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct alternative: "The skin of the baby is very __________."
2;321;Básico;Adjectives;Complete the sentence: "Usually, people with __________ hair want to have curly hair."
2;322;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct answer: "Basketball players are usually __________."
2;323;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct alternative: "I'm not feeling comfortable. My jeans are very __________."
2;324;Básico;Adjectives;Complete the sentence: "She's feeling __________ because she doesn't eat properly."
2;325;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct answer: "__________ people have lots of energy!"
2;326;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct alternative: "Your clothes are very __________. You have to buy new ones."
2;327;Básico;Adjectives;Complete the sentence: "Tigers are very __________. They can run at 65 km/h!"
2;328;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct answer: "The fridge is __________. I have to go shopping for food."
2;329;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct alternative: "Sarah can't play basketball because she is very __________."
2;330;Básico;Adjectives;Complete the sentence: "My children are very __________ at maths. I have to help them study."
2;331;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct answer: "I don't like to tie my hair. I prefer it __________."
2;332;Básico;Adjectives;Complete the sentence: "These exercises are very __________. Can you help me with this question, please?"
2;333;Básico;Adjectives;Complete the sentence: "My brother calls his girlfriend every 5 minutes. He's so __________!"
2;334;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct alternative: "Be careful, the waves at the beach are __________!"
2;335;Básico;Adjectives;Complete the sentence: "He washes and waxes his car every week. It always looks very __________."
2;336;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct alternative: "On __________ days, I don't even have time to eat." 
2;337;Básico;Adjectives;Complete the sentence: "Andrew has a very __________ pronunciation."
2;338;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct alternative: "I think Kevin Spacey is a __________ actor. I love his movies."
2;339;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct alternative: "It is very important to develop __________ eating habits."
2;340;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the best alternative: "I don't agree with Frank's behavior. He's being __________."
2;341;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct alternative: "These boxes are too __________ for me to lift. They weigh too much."
2;342;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the incorrect alternative: "There is a __________ collection of musical instruments in the Metropolitan Museum of Art."
2;343;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the incorrect alternative: "Don't pay attention to them, please. They are just being __________."
2;344;Básico;Adjectives;Complete the sentence: "I liked this TV, but I can't afford it. It's too __________."
2;345;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct answer: "What's the weather like in your city?"
2;346;Básico;Adjectives;Complete the sentence: "Sally is always on the phone. She is very __________."
2;347;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct answer: xptoMatt: "Do you like nightclubs?"xptoFred: "No, they are too __________."
2;348;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct alternative: "My mum always makes me laugh. She is very __________."
2;349;Básico;Adjectives;Complete the sentence: "Are you still in bed at lunch time? You're so __________!"
2;350;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct answer: "I really liked those boots, but they are so __________."
2;351;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct alternative: "I don't really like __________ clothes."
2;352;Básico;Adjectives;Complete the sentence: "I love Abby. She makes friends very easily. She is very __________."
2;353;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct answer: "Please, don't speak with me. I am very __________."
2;354;Básico;Adjectives;Complete the sentence: "What's for dinner? I'm very __________."
2;355;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct alternative: "I really like children. They are very __________."
2;356;Básico;Adjectives;Complete the sentence: "I loved it! It was an __________ and __________ experience."
2;357;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct pair of opposites:
2;358;Básico;Adjectives;What is the opposite of tall?
2;359;Básico;Adjectives;What is the opposite of strong?
2;360;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct pair of opposites:
2;361;Básico;Adjectives;Complete the sentence: "I didn't do well in the test. It was very __________."
2;362;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct answer: "We had a great time in Miami! It was __________."
2;363;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct alternative: "My cousin talks too much. It's __________."
2;364;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct pair of opposites:
2;365;Básico;Adjectives;Complete the sentence: "Tina's hair isn't straight! It's __________."
2;366;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct answer: "My hair isn't short. It's __________."
2;367;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct alternative: "He isn't ugly. Actually, I think he's __________."
2;368;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the best alternative: "I love this restaurant! We should order the __________ burger with __________ sauce." 
2;369;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the best alternative: "I'm so happy our new printer is __________. The previous one was very __________!"
2;370;Básico;Adjectives;Complete the sentence: "He is a __________ cook. He cooks very __________."
2;371;Básico;Adjectives;Complete the sentence: "The test was OK. The questions were quite __________."
2;372;Básico;Adjectives;Which word is not a synonym for "small"?
2;373;Básico;Adjectives;What is a synonym for "clever"?
2;374;Básico;Adjectives;If you are active, it means you are not:
2;375;Básico;Adjectives;Which word is not a synonym for "fast"?
2;376;Básico;Adjectives;Complete the sentence: "I like my new boss, she's really __________."
2;377;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct alternative: "This dress is pretty, but it is a little __________."
2;378;Básico;Adjectives;Complete the sentence: "The new exhibition of the modern art museum is __________."
2;379;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct alternative: "Your office chair looks very __________."
2;380;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the incorrect alternative: "There are many __________ places to visit in this city. I'm very excited."
2;381;Básico;Adjectives;Complete the sentence: "I saw some __________ paintings at the museum yesterday."
2;382;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct alternative: "My boss asked me an __________ question."
2;383;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct alternative: "__________ people are always smiling."
2;384;Básico;Adjectives;Complete the sentence: "They don't have any money. They are very __________."
2;385;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct answer: "Summer in Brazil is usually very __________."
2;386;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct alternative: "Jess doesn't like going to rock concerts because they are very __________."
2;387;Básico;Adjectives;Complete the sentence: "I don't like watching long movies. I prefer __________ movies."
2;388;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct answer: "My maths teacher is very __________. Everybody sleeps during her class."
2;389;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct alternative: "I don't like going to __________ beaches. I prefer the empty ones."
2;390;Básico;Adjectives;Complete the sentence: "Adam never wants to do anything. He is very __________."
2;391;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct answer: "Ann doesn't like speaking with strangers. She is very __________."
2;392;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct alternative: "Jess only does what she wants. She is very __________."
2;393;Básico;Adjectives;Complete the sentence: "I always have to clean the house after my grandson visits me. He is very __________."
2;394;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct answer: "Tessa works a lot. She is very __________."
2;395;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct alternative: "Paul never tells the truth. He is very __________."
2;396;Básico;Adjectives;Complete the sentence: "Their children never say 'thank you'. They are very __________."
2;397;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct answer: "Tom always drinks and drives. He is very __________."
2;398;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct alternative: "Some people don't like waiting. They are very __________."
2;399;Básico;Adjectives;Complete the sentence: "Ann always arrives at work on time. She is very __________."
2;400;Básico;Adjectives;Choose the correct answer: "My friend always talks a lot. He is very __________."
2;401;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative: "__________ is your next business meeting?"
2;402;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct answer: "__________ do you go to school every day?" 
2;403;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ is the bus fare where you live?" 
2;404;Básico;Question words;Complete the sentence: "_______________ are the tickets to the concert?" 
2;405;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct answer: "_______________ people are there in Chicago?" 
2;406;Básico;Question words;Complete the sentence: "_______________ is Tom's grandmother?" 
2;407;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct answer: "_______________ does your son visit you?" 
2;408;Básico;Question words;Complete the sentence: "_______________ is New York from Chicago?"
2;409;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct answer: "_______________ does it take from here to Boston?"
2;410;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative: "__________ is this in your bag? It is a pencil." 
2;411;Básico;Question words;Complete the sentence: "_______________ music do you listen to?" 
2;412;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct answer: "_______________ do you pick up the children at school?" 
2;413;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative: "__________ is your 11th wedding anniversary?"
2;414;Básico;Question words;Complete the sentence: "__________ are you going after work?" 
2;415;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct answer: "__________ is that girl in the blue dress?" 
2;416;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative: "__________ do you usually have lunch with?"
2;417;Básico;Question words;Complete the sentence: "__________ do you normally spend your holidays with?"
2;418;Básico;Question words;Complete the dialogue:xptoPaul: "__________ jacket is this?"xptoTina: "It's Janet's."
2;419;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct answer: "__________ made the donation?"
2;420;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative: "__________ broke my guitar?"
2;421;Básico;Question words;Complete the question: "__________ often do you have French classes?"
2;422;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative: "__________ much does this jacket cost?"
2;423;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct answer: "__________ do you make these delicious cookies? Can you give me the recipe?"
2;424;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ do you take to the airport by bus?"
2;425;Básico;Question words;Complete the sentence: "_______________ do you pay to get your hair cut?"
2;426;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct answer: "_______________ students are there in your class?"
2;427;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ is your nephew? __________ is his birthday?"
2;428;Básico;Question words;Complete the sentence: "_______________ do you take martial arts classes?"
2;429;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct answer: "__________ do you usually have for dinner?"
2;430;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ books do you like reading?"
2;431;Básico;Question words;Complete the sentence: "_______________ do you usually go to bed?"
2;432;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct answer: "_______________ does you father usually get home?"
2;433;Básico;Question words;Choose the best alternative: "What kind of car _______________?"
2;434;Básico;Question words;Complete the question: "__________ do your parents do?"
2;435;Básico;Question words;Complete the question:xptoSandra: "_______________ the last time you traveled abroad?"xptoChris: "It was 5 years ago."
2;436;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative:xptoAimee: "__________ is the Louvre?"xptoPeter: "It is a museum."
2;437;Básico;Question words;Complete the question:xptoJohn: "__________ is the capital of France?"xptoTom: "It is Paris."
2;438;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative:xptoAnn: "__________ is Tom Cruise?"xptoPaula: "He is an actor."
2;439;Básico;Question words;Complete the question:xptoMick: "__________ is Carnival in Rio de Janeiro?"xptoTed: "It is usually in February." 
2;440;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ does it cost to fly to Buenos Aires?"
2;441;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct answer: "_______________ apples do we have to buy?"
2;442;Básico;Question words;Complete the question: "__________ is the Sahara desert?"
2;443;Básico;Question words;Complete the dialogue:xptoKate: "__________ are the Andes Mountains?"xptoJohn: "They are in South America."
2;444;Básico;Question words;Complete the question: "__________ dress do you prefer? The white one or the black one?"
2;445;Básico;Question words;Complete the dialogue:xptoMark: "__________ is the New York Times?"xptoPeter: "It is an American newspaper."
2;446;Básico;Question words;Match the question to the answer: "Because I woke up too early."
2;447;Básico;Question words;Complete the question:xptoSuzy: "Why __________ open the window?"xptoCarl: "Because it's cold."
2;448;Básico;Question words;Complete the question:xptoSarah: "When __________ your parents __________ to Europe?"xptoJane: "Last January."
2;449;Básico;Question words;Complete the question: "_______________ going tomorrow? To the city center?"
2;450;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative: "__________ time does the movie __________?"
2;451;Básico;Question words;Complete the question: "__________ is your favorite TV show about?"
2;452;Básico;Question words;Complete the question: "__________ is more dangerous: hiking in Canada or surfing in Australia?"
2;453;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative: "__________ do you think that man is waiting for? His wife?"
2;454;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct answer: "__________ is his favorite author?"
2;455;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative: "__________ does Tom live?"
2;456;Básico;Question words;Complete the sentence: "__________ do you prefer: lamb or chicken?"
2;457;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct answer: "__________ do you usually spend your holidays?"
2;458;Básico;Question words;Complete the dialogue: xptoTim: "__________ keys are these?"xptoAnn: "They are my keys." 
2;459;Básico;Question words;Complete the dialogue: xptoJohn: "_______________ is the movie?"xptoTessa: "It's about 2 hours long." 
2;460;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative: "__________ do you usually do on weekends?" 
2;461;Básico;Question words;Complete the sentence: "_______________ do you usually arrive from work?" 
2;462;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct answer: "_______________ do you go to the movies?" 
2;463;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative: "__________ is the car?" 
2;464;Básico;Question words;Complete the sentence: "__________ don't you come with us?" 
2;465;Básico;Question words;Choose the best question for the following answer: "Yesterday."
2;466;Básico;Question words;Complete the question: "What __________ he do for a living? He is an architect."
2;467;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative to complete the question. "Where _______________ find a pen?"
2;468;Básico;Question words;Choose the incorrect alternative: xptoSusan: "How does he drive?"xptoBart: "__________."
2;469;Básico;Question words;Fill in the gap with the correct alternative: "When __________ your birthday?"
2;470;Básico;Question words;Complete the question: xptoJames: " __________ is the meeting room?"xptoMichelle: "Downstairs."
2;471;Básico;Question words;Complete the question: "I'm organizing a party. __________ can came?"
2;472;Básico;Question words;Match the question to the answer: "Because I had too much to do."
2;473;Básico;Question words;Complete the question: "What time __________ the bus __________?"
2;474;Básico;Question words;Choose the incorrect alternative: "Where are you __________ ?"
2;475;Básico;Question words;Complete the question: xptoNicolas: "__________ does he work?" xptoRobert: "He works downtown."
2;476;Básico;Question words;Choose the best alternative: "I like your bag. __________ did you buy it?"
2;477;Básico;Question words;Complete the question: "Who __________ in that apartment?"
2;478;Básico;Question words;Complete the sentence: "Excuse me, __________ the subway station, please?"
2;479;Básico;Question words;Complete the question: "_______________ your mother's name?
2;480;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative: "__________ many letters are there in your name?"
2;481;Básico;Question words;Complete the question: "_______________ the president of your country?"
2;482;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative: "__________ country is your father from?"
2;483;Básico;Question words;Complete the question: "__________ my pen? I need to sign this document."
2;484;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative: "__________ much does it cost to fly to Japan?"
2;485;Básico;Question words;Complete the sentence: "There is a cat in our front yard. __________ is it?"
2;486;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct answer: "__________ does Tom usually get home from school?"
2;487;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ do you pay for rent every month?"
2;488;Básico;Question words;Complete the sentence: "_______________ people are coming to the party next Saturday?"
2;489;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct answer: "_______________ is your dog?"
2;490;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ does Ted take guitar lessons?"
2;491;Básico;Question words;Complete the sentence: "__________ are you crying? Don't cry. It's going to be all right."
2;492;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct answer: "__________ are you so nervous? Just relax and take a deep breath."
2;493;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ does it take to fly from New York to Chicago?"
2;494;Básico;Question words;Complete the sentence: "__________ do you do every day after dinner?"
2;495;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct answer: "_______________ sport do you do?"
2;496;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ does Jennifer finish work every day?"
2;497;Básico;Question words;Complete the sentence: "__________ is Jenn's 30th birthday?"
2;498;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct answer: "__________ is your favorite place to eat in New York?"
2;499;Básico;Question words;Choose the correct alternative: "__________ is your favorite? Thai or Mexican food?"
2;500;Básico;Question words;Complete the sentence: "There is a pair of sunglasses on the table. __________ is it?"
2;501;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the sentence: "My daughter has __________ dog. Its name is Lilly." 
2;502;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the sentence: "We need __________ glass of milk and __________ egg for the recipe."
2;503;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the sentence: "Please, bring __________ bottle of wine and __________ ice."
2;504;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Choose the correct alternative: "Let's buy __________ pasta and __________ bottle of champagne for her birthday party."
2;505;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the sentence: "I saw __________ ostrich and __________ parrot in the zoo last weekend."
2;506;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Choose the correct alternative: "February is __________ exciting month and __________ good moment to come to Brazil."
2;507;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the sentence: "It was quite __________ adventure, I had a lot of fun!"
2;508;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the sentence: "I have __________ important question to ask my boss."
2;509;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Choose the correct alternative: "Catherine is staying in _________ very good hotel downtown."
2;510;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the sentence: "Luc and his family own __________ antique shop in the city center."
2;511;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Choose the correct alternative: "I found __________ old photograph as I was cleaning my room."
2;512;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the sentence: "I met __________ old friend at the cinema last night."
2;513;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Choose the correct alternative: "Sometimes it is hard to make ___________ intelligent decision."
2;514;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the sentence: "Susan is an__________ and dedicated professional."
2;515;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Choose the correct alternative: "The war ended because the opponents came to __________ agreement."
2;516;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the sentence: "I live in __________ apartment near the City Hall."
2;517;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Choose the correct answer: "It's very cold today. I think I'll make us __________ tea."
2;518;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Choose the correct alternative: "I always drink __________ coffee when I wake up."
2;519;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the sentence: "It's very hot today. We are going to get __________ ice cream cone."
2;520;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the question: "Do you have __________ brothers or sisters?"
2;521;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Choose the correct answer: "There's __________ box on the table. What's in it?"
2;522;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Choose the correct alternative: "Open the curtains and let __________ light in!"
2;523;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the sentence: "I have __________ information to give you."
2;524;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Choose the correct alternative: "I don't have __________ information about her flight."
2;525;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the sentence: "I'm thirsty. Can I have __________ water, please?"
2;526;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Choose the correct alternative: "I have to finish making this cake but there isn't __________ flour left."
2;527;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the dialogue:xptoJulie: "I'm very tired today."xptoSam: "Would you like __________ coffee?"
2;528;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Choose the correct alternative: "There's nothing better than __________ cup of coffee to start the day."
2;529;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the sentence: "There are __________ few oranges in the refrigerator. I'll make __________ juice." 
2;530;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the dialogue:xptoMark: "What will you have to drink with your pasta?"xptoSue: "I'll have __________ glass of wine, please."
2;531;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Choose the correct alternative: "I want to make __________ juice but there aren't __________ lemons left."
2;532;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Which words are countable nouns?
2;533;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the sentence: "Please give me __________ minute. I need __________ air."
2;534;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Choose the correct alternative: "I need __________ time to think about it."
2;535;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the sentence: "Your son needs __________ advice."
2;536;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the sentence: "__________ weather is beautiful today. We should have __________ ice-cream at the park."
2;537;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Choose the correct alternative: "When she was a child, she wanted to be __________ actress, but now she is __________ designer."
2;538;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the question: "Do we have carrots for the salad? I can't find __________."
2;539;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the sentence: "There isn't __________ juice in the fridge."
2;540;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Find the pair of uncountable nouns:
2;541;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the question: "Is there __________ illegal item in your bag, sir?"
2;542;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Choose the correct alternative: "I'm sad because I still don't have __________ friends in this city."
2;543;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Choose the incorrect alternative: "There's an __________ restaurant on my street."
2;544;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Choose the best alternative: "I'm studying to be an __________."
2;545;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the sentence: "When I was __________ child, I wanted to become __________ astronaut."
2;546;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the sentence: "I can't do it all by myself. I need __________ help."
2;547;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the sentence: "__________ island is a piece of land surrounded by water."
2;548;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Choose the best answer: "She had __________ accident last year."
2;549;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the sentence: "There was __________ earthquake in Japan yesterday."
2;550;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Choose the correct alternative: "Can you lend me __________ money? I need to pay my bills."
2;551;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the sentence with the best alternative: "I have __________ idea. Let's go to __________ Japanese restaurant."
2;552;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Choose the best alternative: "I know __________ Australian surfer who was attacked by __________ shark."
2;553;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the sentence: "Do you have __________ idea of what he is saying?"
2;554;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Choose the best alternative: "You need to get __________ new cell phone."
2;555;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Choose the incorrect alternative: '"There are __________ books I want to read this year."
2;556;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the sentence: "Paul is studying hard to be __________ architect."
2;557;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Choose the best alternative: "Excuse me, can I have __________ sugar in my coffee please?"
2;558;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the sentence: "Would you like __________ help?"
2;559;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the sentence: "There aren't __________ restaurants in this neighborhood."
2;560;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Choose the correct alternative: "My uncle __________ famous artist".
2;561;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Choose the correct alternative: "I would like __________ omelet and __________ piece of cake, please."
2;562;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the sentence: "We have __________ house in the mountains."
2;563;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the sentence: "I'm not sure. I need __________ days to think about it."
2;564;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Choose the correct alternative: "Let me boil __________ water for the coffee."
2;565;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the sentence : "I bought __________ furniture for my new house this week: __________ wardrobe, a sofa and a bed."
2;566;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the sentence: "Excuse me sir, would you like __________ wine and __________ glass of water with your food?"
2;567;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Choose the correct alternative to complete the sentence: "__________ of the fruits in the fridge __________ rotten."
2;568;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Which words are uncountable nouns?
2;569;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Choose the countable noun:
2;570;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Which word is not a plural form?
2;571;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the question: "Do you have __________ pets at home?"
2;572;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Choose the correct answer: "I think they're home. There's __________ car parked in the garage."
2;573;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Choose the correct alternative: "Tim is a __________ student."
2;574;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the sentence: "I'm going to the bakery to buy __________ loaf of bread."
2;575;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the question: "Can you bring me __________ glass of wine, please?"
2;576;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Choose the correct answer: "I have spilled __________ wine on my sweater."
2;577;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Choose the correct alternative: "I love lying down and listening to __________ music."
2;578;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the sentence: "The band played __________ great music last night."
2;579;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the question: "Can you turn up the volume, please? That's __________ great song!"
2;580;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Choose the correct answer: "When I travel I never take __________ baggage with me."
2;581;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Choose the correct alternative: "Joan is going shopping. She wants to buy __________ new pair of jeans."
2;582;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the sentence: "I want to donate __________ of my clothes."
2;583;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the question: "Is there __________ new furniture in your new house?"
2;584;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Choose the correct answer: "I have to iron my pants. Do you have __________ iron?"
2;585;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Choose the correct alternative: "I need __________ information on Latin America for my research."
2;586;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the sentence: "When I travel I always take __________ book with me."
2;587;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the question: "Do you have __________ information about the weather today?"
2;588;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Choose the correct answer: "I know __________ people who do yoga. They love it!"
2;589;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Choose the correct alternative: "We need __________ wood to make a fire."
2;590;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the sentence: "I had __________ bread and __________ cup of coffee for breakfast."
2;591;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the question: "Would you like __________ cheese and ham sandwich?"
2;592;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Choose the correct answer: "I want __________ piece of cake for dessert."
2;593;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Choose the correct alternative: "I would like __________ butter on my toast, please."
2;594;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the sentence: "My children usually drink __________ glass of milk before going to bed."
2;595;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the question: "Are there __________ towels in the bathroom?"
2;596;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Choose the correct answer: "There aren't __________ bus stops in this street."
2;597;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Choose the correct alternative: "There aren't __________ hospitals in this neighborhood."
2;598;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the sentence: "There aren't __________ pet shops near the university."
2;599;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Complete the question: "Are there __________ coffee shops open at night around here?"
2;600;Básico;Countable and uncountable nouns;Choose the correct answer: "I saw __________ elephant when I was in Africa."
2;601;Básico;There is / There are;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ a wonderful beach near our hotel, I'm impressed!"
2;602;Básico;There is / There are;Choose the correct alternative: "There _______________ any juice in the fridge."
2;603;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the question: "_______________ a swimming pool in your house?"
2;604;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the question: "_______________ chairs in your barbecue area?"
2;605;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the question: "_______________ many job opportunities in your city?"
2;606;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the question: "How many stamps _______________ in your collection?"
2;607;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the question: "How much juice _______________ in the bottle?"
2;608;Básico;There is / There are;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ any cherry trees in the Japanese garden?"
2;609;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the question: "How many meeting rooms _______________ in your office building?"
2;610;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the question: "_______________ enough tables in the party room?"
2;611;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the question: "Why _______________ so many cars on that street?"
2;612;Básico;There is / There are;Choose the correct alternative: "There __________ a lot of traffic in the city I live. It's terrible!"
2;613;Básico;There is / There are;Choose the correct alternative: "There __________ lots of foreign people in my class this year."
2;614;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the sentence: "Watch out! _______________ a spider in the grass."
2;615;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the sentence: "What should I do now? _______________ three forks next to my plate!"
2;616;Básico;There is / There are;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ too many children in the park today."
2;617;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the sentence: "_______________ enough computers in the computer lab. I always have to wait in the line."
2;618;Básico;There is / There are;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ any restaurants on this road. We'll have to wait a little longer."
2;619;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the sentence: "_______________ some cookies in the jar. Please, help yourself."
2;620;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the sentence: "There __________ too many slices of cheese on my sandwich. More than ten!"
2;621;Básico;There is / There are;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ a lot of salt in this salad. It's very salty!"
2;622;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the sentence: "_______________ a subway station near our new apartment. We don't need to use the car."
2;623;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the sentence: "_______________ so many cars in the parking lot that I don't know if you'll find a parking spot."
2;624;Básico;There is / There are;Fill in the gap with the correct alternative: "Look at these dark clouds. _______________ a big storm coming this way."
2;625;Básico;There is / There are;Choose the correct answer: "_______________ lots of stores in 5th Avenue in New York. Let's go shopping there."
2;626;Básico;There is / There are;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ a restaurant next to your house?"
2;627;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the sentence: "_______________ a big living room in my apartment. We can have the party there."
2;628;Básico;There is / There are;Choose the correct answer: "_______________ two bedrooms in my house. You can have one."
2;629;Básico;There is / There are;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ a bathroom I can use?"
2;630;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the sentence: "_______________ any letters to Mrs. Smith?"
2;631;Básico;There is / There are;Choose the correct answer: "_______________ any milk in the fridge?"
2;632;Básico;There is / There are;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ any seats available?"
2;633;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the sentence: "_______________ any water in the bottle?"
2;634;Básico;There is / There are;Choose the correct answer: "_______________ some eggs in the fridge. Let's make a cake!"
2;635;Básico;There is / There are;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ a dog in the front yard. Do you know its name?"
2;636;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the sentence: "_______________ a new movie on TV tonight. Let's watch it!"
2;637;Básico;There is / There are;Choose the correct answer: "_______________ any good movies on TV tonight?"
2;638;Básico;There is / There are;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ a new student in my class. Her name is Jessica."
2;639;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the sentence: "_______________ a new employee at the company where I work. His name is John."
2;640;Básico;There is / There are;Choose the correct answer: "_______________ any new information about the accident?"
2;641;Básico;There is / There are;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ some people who never travel. They don't like it."
2;642;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the sentence: "_______________ twenty listening questions on the test."
2;643;Básico;There is / There are;Choose the correct alternative: "How many bedrooms _______________ in this apartment?"
2;644;Básico;There is / There are;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ any donuts left? I need something sweet."
2;645;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the sentence:"_______________ many different animals in this zoo."
2;646;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the sentence: "There __________ something different about Sally today."
2;647;Básico;There is / There are;Choose the incorrect alternative: "There __________ ten people working in my department."
2;648;Básico;There is / There are;Choose the best answer: "There __________ restrooms downstairs."
2;649;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the sentence: " _______________ many beautiful trees in that park."
2;650;Básico;There is / There are;Choose the best alternative: "There __________ 120 rooms in the hotel."
2;651;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the sentence: "_______________ a new café downtown that sells wonderful pies."
2;652;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the sentence: "There __________ is the plural form of there __________."
2;653;Básico;There is / There are;Choose the correct alternative:" _______________ good restaurants in your neighborhood?"
2;654;Básico;There is / There are;Choose the best alternative: "There __________ too much pepper on my sauce."
2;655;Básico;There is / There are;Choose the correct alternative: "How many oceans _______________? Four or five?"
2;656;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the sentence: "_______________ approximately thirty people in my office."
2;657;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the sentence: "_______________ a nice bar near our apartment."
2;658;Básico;There is / There are;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ thirty-two apartments in each building."
2;659;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the sentence: "I'm going to be late. _______________ too much traffic."
2;660;Básico;There is / There are;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ many things you can do lose weight."
2;661;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the sentence: " _______________ very good actors in this movie."
2;662;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the sentence: "_______________ a lot of __________ in this hospital."
2;663;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the dialogue:xptoJanice: "How many days _______________ in March?"xptoPaul:    " Thirty-one."
2;664;Básico;There is / There are;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ a lot of museums in New York City."
2;665;Básico;There is / There are;Choose the best alternative: "I can help you with your work. _______________ a lot of things to do."
2;666;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the sentence: "Even though it's raining, _______________ many children playing in the streets."
2;667;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the sentence: "_______________ any water in the fridge."
2;668;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the dialogue:xptoJill: "_______________ a bus coming soon?"xptoJohn: "Yes, and it's going downtown."
2;669;Básico;There is / There are;Choose the correct alternative: "Don't worry, _______________ enough time to get there."
2;670;Básico;There is / There are;Choose the best alternative: "Oh no, _______________ any oranges left!"
2;671;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the dialogue:xptoSue: "I'm very busy."xptoMark: "_______________ anything I can do to help you?"
2;672;Básico;There is / There are;Choose the correct alternative: "Good job! We've finished everything! _______________ nothing left to do."
2;673;Básico;There is / There are;Choose the best alternative: "I'm sorry. _______________ any seats available."
2;674;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the dialogue:xptoThomas: "Oh no, I missed the bus!"xptoMartha: "Don't worry, _______________ buses every 30 minutes in the morning."
2;675;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the sentence: "_______________ more girls than boys in her class."
2;676;Básico;There is / There are;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ too many people in this bus."
2;677;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the sentence: "I am sorry. _______________ nothing I can do to help you."
2;678;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the question: "How many people _______________ in this party?"
2;679;Básico;There is / There are;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ a very nice restaurant in our hotel. I loved it!"
2;680;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the sentence: "Don't worry, you can invite them all. I'm sure _______________ room for everyone in our house."
2;681;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the question: "_______________ any fruits in the fridge?"
2;682;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the sentence: "_______________ a store near my apartment that has everything you need."
2;683;Básico;There is / There are;Choose the correct alternative: "Well, I think_______________ nothing I can do to change your opinion."
2;684;Básico;There is / There are;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ something in this book that I don't understand."
2;685;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the sentence: "__________ a photography exhibition at the modern art museum this week. Would you like to go with me?"
2;686;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the sentence: "__________ 3 doctors and 4 biologists in our research group."
2;687;Básico;There is / There are;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ 11 bedrooms in this castle. Isn't it amazing?"
2;688;Básico;There is / There are;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ some water in the fridge, in case you like it cold."
2;689;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the sentence: "_______________ many ways of helping people in need."
2;690;Básico;There is / There are;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ two lemon trees in my garden."
2;691;Básico;There is / There are;Choose the correct alternative: "How many days _______________ in two years?"
2;692;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the question: "How many players _______________ in a basketball team?"
2;693;Básico;There is / There are;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ a big black cloud in the sky. I think it's going to rain."
2;694;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the sentence: " I heard _______________ a big storm coming towards our city. Let's not go outside."
2;695;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the sentence: "Why _______________ so many people on the streets today?"
2;696;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the sentence: "_______________ many parks in Canada. It's a beautiful country."
2;697;Básico;There is / There are;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ a lot of space in this apartment. I like it."
2;698;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the sentence: "There __________ only one problem with this wonderful house. It is really expensive."
2;699;Básico;There is / There are;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ a black car parked in front of your house. Is it yours?"
2;700;Básico;There is / There are;Complete the question: "How many people _______________ in your family?"
2;701;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "_______________ go to the museum today. It's closed."
2;702;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the question: "_______________ understand French?"
2;703;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "_______________ stay with my brother while we're in London. He'll be happy to have us."
2;704;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "_______________ hand me the pen, please? I need to sign this contract."
2;705;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "______________ cross the road when the light is red."
2;706;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the question: "_______________ help me find the documents, please?"
2;707;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "I know her, but I __________ remember her name."
2;708;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "The president __________ talk to you right now. He's busy."
2;709;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "I __________ travel with you next month because I don't have any money."
2;710;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the dialogue: xptoStudent: "Do I have to use a pencil?"xptoTeacher: "No, you __________ use a pen, if you prefer."
2;711;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the dialogue:xptoSecretary: "Mr. Anderson is out of the office right now."xptoBryan: "OK, _______________ leave a message?"
2;712;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the question: "Excuse me, _______________ take a picture of us, please?"
2;713;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "_______________ discuss this later? I'm really busy right now."
2;714;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "_______________ turn the volume down, please? _______________ concentrate on my work."
2;715;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the question: "_______________ close the door, please? It's very cold in here."
2;716;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the question: "_______________ switch on the light? It's dark in here."
2;717;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ believe I forgot to bring my camera. Look at all these beautiful places."
2;718;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "My brother __________ surf, but he __________ swim."
2;719;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "My sister __________ swim a hundred meters in 1 minute. That's really fast!"
2;720;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the question: "_______________ start a fire without a match? It's very hard."
2;721;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "Paul doesn't want to go on the boat trip because he __________ swim."
2;722;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ have dinner with us tonight if you want. I'll cook."
2;723;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "Elephants __________ swim, but they __________ climb trees."
2;724;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "Dogs __________ speak, but they __________ bark."
2;725;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the dialogue: xptoMark: "How many languages __________ you speak?"xptoAnn: "I can speak 3 languages: Portuguese, Spanish, and English."
2;726;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct answer: "You usually __________ take pictures inside museums."
2;727;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "People __________ read books at libraries."
2;728;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "I'm going to take guitar lessons because _______________ play the guitar very well."
2;729;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the question: "_______________ see the menu? I want to check out the prices."
2;730;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct answer: "Mike is going to take swimming lessons because he __________ swim very well."
2;731;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "There is a very nice store in 5th Avenue. You __________ find something nice there."
2;732;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "She has lived in France for 10 years, so she __________ speak French very well."
2;733;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the question: "__________ you give me directions to the mall? I want to go shopping."
2;734;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct answer: "There are many countries where women __________ vote. We have to change that."
2;735;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "Batman is a superhero that __________ fly."
2;736;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "If the weather is good, _______________ ride your bike to school."
2;737;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "I_________ go swimming this week because I'm sick."
2;738;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "_______________ play any instrument? _______________ play the guitar."
2;739;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ play any sports?"
2;740;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the question: "_______________ write with your left hand?"
2;741;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "I __________ cook pasta, but I __________ cook meat. I'm a vegetarian."
2;742;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the dialogue:xptoBruce: "______________ surf?"xptoAmy: "No, _______________."
2;743;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the question: "Where _______________ smoke?"
2;744;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ help me in the garden?"
2;745;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "This neighborhood is very peaceful. _______________ hear the birds singing?"
2;746;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the dialogue: xptoSandra: "__________ speak French?" xptoThomas: "No, _______________."
2;747;Básico;Can / Can't;Fill in the gap with the correct alternative: "__________ help me here, please? These boxes are too heavy."
2;748;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the best alternative: "_______________ help me? I __________ find this street on the map."
2;749;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "She is a very good teacher. She __________ help you with that."
2;750;Básico;Can / Can't;Which of the following answers is incorrect?: "Can you bring me some water on your way back?" 
2;751;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the best option to complete the dialogue: "Can you help me take these books upstairs?"
2;752;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "________________ use your cell phone for a second please? I need to call my mom."
2;753;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the best alternative: "John can __________ seven languages."
2;754;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the question: "Excuse me, ______________ have a glass of water, please?"
2;755;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "I'm sorry, _______________ talk to you right now. She's on a phone call."
2;756;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "I can drive, but _______________ ride a motorcycle." 
2;757;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "_______________ use your phone charger, please?"
2;758;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "Sometimes in stories, _______________."
2;759;Básico;Can / Can't;Which of the following sentences is correct?
2;760;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "Oh no, _______________ remember where I left my keys."
2;761;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the best alternative: "Cats __________ climb trees but __________ fly."
2;762;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the question: "__________ dogs swim?"
2;763;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "Birds __________ fly and sing."
2;764;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the dialogue:xptoSandra: "Where __________ I buy stamps?"xptoMark: "At the post office."
2;765;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the dialogue:xptoSue: "__________ you ride horses?"xptoJohn: "No, I __________."
2;766;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "Have you seen my bag? I __________ find it anywhere!"
2;767;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "__________ you call me again? I __________ hear you!"
2;768;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct answer: "Ann's got the job because she __________ speak three languages."
2;769;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the dialogue:xptoTed: "__________ you come to my party on Friday?"xptoSarah: "No, I'm sorry, we __________."
2;770;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "This hotel room is amazing! I __________ see the mountains from the window!"
2;771;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "Hello? _______________ hear me? My cell phone is not working very well."
2;772;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "I think I'm in love, _______________ stop thinking of her."
2;773;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ ask you a personal question? Are you married?"
2;774;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "_______________ to the movies with you. I have to study a lot tonight."
2;775;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "_______________ believe you don't like chocolate, I love it!"
2;776;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "I'm sorry if it's not a good time but _______________ help me with this contract?"
2;777;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "I'm sorry, I _______________ you very well. _______________ say it again, please?"
2;778;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "Some things __________ be explained. They are inexplicable."
2;779;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "_______________ smoke here, but you __________ smoke outside."
2;780;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "_______________ play volleyball? I __________ play any sports."
2;781;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "Our daughter is ill, so we _______________ come to your birthday party tonight. I'm sorry."
2;782;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ speak louder, please? I _______________ hear you."
2;783;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "_______________ open the door for me, please? These boxes are very heavy."
2;784;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "_______________ try a bit of your cake? It smells really good."
2;785;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "Do you have a dictionary to lend me? I __________ understand this word."
2;786;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct answer: "_______________ use your phone, please? I have to call my mother."
2;787;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "It's cold, so the children __________ go to the beach today. They are going to get sick."
2;788;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "I __________ open the door because I don't have the key."
2;789;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct answer: "Kelly __________ work in the garden today because it's raining."
2;790;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "Tom __________ use my computer today because it's out of battery."
2;791;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "You __________ water the plants three times a day. It's bad for them."
2;792;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the question: "__________ I go out with my friends tonight? We are going to a nightclub in town."
2;793;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct answer: "On Fridays the children __________ bring their toys to school. They have lots of fun!"
2;794;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "My baby is 1 month old. He __________ walk yet."
2;795;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "Matt __________ go swimming because it is very cold."
2;796;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the dialogue: xptoWilliam: "__________ we have ice cream for dessert?"xptoMrs. Smith: "Yes, you ___________."
2;797;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct answer: "Zebras __________ climb trees, but they __________ run very fast."
2;798;Básico;Can / Can't;Which of the following alternatives is incorrect?: " _______________ see the sea from my apartment. _______________ see it from yours?"
2;799;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "_______________ borrow my jacket if you like."
2;800;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "Some people __________ speak more than four languages. I find it amazing."
2;801;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "Cary and Bruce __________  a lot of money on their last vacation."
2;802;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "I __________ my husband downtown and we __________ home for dinner."
2;803;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "I __________ lost in the city center this morning, but a kind man __________ me."
2;804;Básico;Past simple;Complete the question: "Did your friend _________ you to keep the news a secret?"
2;805;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "I didn't __________ this report. Sarah __________ it."
2;806;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "Yesterday was a beautiful day, we __________ to the beach and __________ in the sea."
2;807;Básico;Past simple;Complete the dialogue:xptoOlivia: "Where did you buy this shirt?"xptoCary: "I didn't _________ it, it __________ a birthday present."
2;808;Básico;Past simple;Complete the dialogue:xptoMary: "Did you __________ your birthday party?"xptoCassia: "Yes, I __________ it, thank you."
2;809;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "She __________ up early this morning and __________ swimming."
2;810;Básico;Past simple;Complete the question: "Where __________ he __________? I was looking for him."
2;811;Básico;Past simple;Complete the question: "What kind of games did you _________ when you __________ a child?"
2;812;Básico;Past simple;Complete the dialogue: xptoSam: "Where __________ you born?"xptoLukas: "I __________ born in Switzerland."
2;813;Básico;Past simple;Complete the question: "What __________ the weather like last weekend?"
2;814;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "We __________ a meeting from 9 to 12 o'clock, then we __________ to an Italian restaurant."
2;815;Básico;Past simple;Complete the question: "What __________ for Cary's birthday?"
2;816;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "He didn't __________ your sister had two children."
2;817;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "I _______________ at work last week. I __________ on vacation."
2;818;Básico;Past simple;Complete the question: "__________ you at the club yesterday? I think I __________ you."
2;819;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "I __________ you mother on the street this morning, but she _______________ me."
2;820;Básico;Past simple;Complete the dialogue:xptoBen: "What time _______________ ?"xptoJoshua: "An hour ago."
2;821;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "My mother and my father __________ married in 1981."
2;822;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "The bus was taking too long, so I __________ a cab to the airport."
2;823;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "I __________ a lot yesterday. __________ pizza, salad, chocolate cake and ice cream."
2;824;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "I think I __________ you last week. __________ at the mall?"
2;825;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "My trip was great. I __________ some really nice people." 
2;826;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "When I __________ in France yesterday, I __________ straight to the Eiffel Tower."
2;827;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "My friends and I __________ to Barbados last vacation. It __________ a fantastic trip."
2;828;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "We __________ to our new house last summer."
2;829;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "I __________ the bus this morning because I __________ up late."
2;830;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "I remember the first time we __________. It __________ a very cold day."
2;831;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "What a coincidence! I _______________ Alice __________ your sister."
2;832;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "I was nervous because the director __________ me to __________ in public."
2;833;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "I __________ your parents on the street this morning. They __________ in a hurry."
2;834;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "Your boss __________ me you are doing a very nice job, congratulations!"
2;835;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "I _______________ you 3 days ago but you _______________."
2;836;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "It was a nice day. The children __________ soccer and __________ kites all day long."
2;837;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "We __________ the hotel where we __________ our last vacation."
2;838;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "Jane __________ my car this morning to __________ her father to the airport."
2;839;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "I closed the windows when it __________ to rain."
2;840;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "My daughter __________ a glass of milk before she __________ for school this morning."
2;841;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "I'm starving. I _______________ anything to eat this morning."
2;842;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "I __________ that you __________ in the hospital yesterday. Are you OK?"
2;843;Básico;Past simple;Fill in the gap with the correct alternative: "I__________ until 10 o'clock this morning, then I went to my friend's house."
2;844;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct answer: "I __________ a new car a week ago."
2;845;Básico;Past simple;Choose the incorrect alternative: I called her __________, but she wasn't home."
2;846;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: " _______________ last weekend?"
2;847;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative:"__________ you __________ a good time at the beach last summer?"
2;848;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "__________ you __________ your work yesterday?"
2;849;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "__________ you __________ to the party yesterday?"
2;850;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "It is my friend's birthday today. I __________ her a present yesterday."
2;851;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "They _______________ to work last week. They were on holiday."
2;852;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "Thomas _______________ to work yesterday because he was ill."
2;853;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "These are the photos that we __________ on our last trip."
2;854;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "He __________ his wife with flowers last night."
2;855;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "Yesterday, I __________ to the supermarket after work."
2;856;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "I __________ some Christmas presents this morning."
2;857;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "I __________ my wallet at home."
2;858;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct answer: "Did you __________ your homework in the morning?"
2;859;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "Two years ago, I __________ to the USA with my family."
2;860;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct answer: "Peter __________ the TV and __________ to bed."
2;861;Básico;Past simple;Complete the question: "__________ you __________ your trip to South Africa last month?"
2;862;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct answer: "Last month, I __________ to Mexico to visit my friends."
2;863;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "Thanks for yesterday. I really _________ the party."
2;864;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "My boss _______________ the meeting this morning. So, I'm free."
2;865;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "I was born in Canada, but I __________ up in the USA."
2;866;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "She __________ all day long after that long flight on Monday."
2;867;Básico;Past simple;Complete the question: "__________ you __________ Tim at school yesterday?"
2;868;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct answer: "Sarah __________ a new iPad last week."
2;869;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "The teacher __________ angry because I _______________ my homework."
2;870;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "Grandma __________ me a nice present for my birthday last year."
2;871;Básico;Past simple;Complete the dialogue: xptoSarah: "__________ Pam finally __________ to Paris last year?"xptoTom: "No, she didn't. She's still living here."
2;872;Básico;Past simple;Complete the question: "Where __________ you __________  last Christmas?"
2;873;Básico;Past simple;Complete the dialogue:xptoAimee: "Where __________ you last night?"xptoPaul: "I __________ at home."
2;874;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct answer: "Jimmy __________ a fantastic book last year."
2;875;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "She __________ all her belongings and __________ to London last month."
2;876;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "He __________ very tired, so he __________ late today."
2;877;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct answer: "Sam __________ the bus one hour ago."
2;878;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "Your phone __________ just a minute ago."
2;879;Básico;Past simple;Complete the dialogue:xptoSue: "Would you like some water?"xptoKaren: "No, thank you. I __________ some just a minute ago."
2;880;Básico;Past simple;Complete the question: "__________ Peter _________ in time for his interview yesterday?"
2;881;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "She __________ jogging after class this morning."
2;882;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct answer: "Mark and John _______________ her the truth in the past."
2;883;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "We _________ them at a party last week."
2;884;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "I __________ my new dress to the party last night."
2;885;Básico;Past simple;Complete the question: "I can't find my glasses anywhere! __________ you ___________ them?
2;886;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "They __________ breakfast and then __________ the kids to school this morning."
2;887;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "Last night you were so tired that you _______________ goodnight." 
2;888;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "Oh, sorry, nobody __________ me it __________ a surprise party."
2;889;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "Yesterday, the weather report __________ it was going to rain today."
2;890;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "Yesterday, I __________ to a concert that __________ three hours."
2;891;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "I __________ too much this afternoon. Now, I have a stomachache."
2;892;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "Last weekend, Pamela and Bryan __________ a train from Paris to Amsterdam."
2;893;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "I __________ to call my aunt on her birthday last Tuesday."
2;894;Básico;Past simple;Complete the dialogue:xptoClaire: "Where did James __________ on his last vacation?"xptoPatrick: "He __________ to Tahiti."
2;895;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "My grandmother __________ me this ring when I turned 30."
2;896;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "Our teacher ________________ to class yesterday because she was sick."
2;897;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "Marcos __________ his CV to a law firm last week, but they didn't __________ him back."
2;898;Básico;Past simple;Choose the correct alternative: "We __________ to study, but it __________ hard to concentrate with all that noise."
2;899;Básico;Past simple;Complete the sentence: "Last time I __________ you, you ___________ just a child."
2;900;Básico;Past simple;Complete the question: "Where __________ you __________ this ring? It's beautiful!"
2;901;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Complete the sentence: "My house is very dirty. I need to hire a __________."
2;902;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Choose the correct answer: "The Storming of the Bastille in France occurred on the __________ of July, 1789."
2;903;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Choose the best answer: "The World Trade Center attacks occurred on the __________ of September, 2001."
2;904;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Choose the correct alternative: "The world population has exceeded __________ billion."
2;905;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Choose the best alternative: "Mike's birthday is on the _______________ of October."
2;906;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Fill in the gap with the correct answer: "My cousin is moving here on the __________ of May."
2;907;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Fill in the gap with the best answer: "World War I ended on the __________ of November, 1918."
2;908;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Fill in the gap with the correct alternative: "World War II began on the __________ of September, 1939."
2;909;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Fill in the gap with the best alternative: "My father has owned this shop since the __________ of January, 1960."
2;910;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Complete the sentence: "I'm the first, you are the second and Alex is the __________."
2;911;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Complete the question: "Do you know anyone who was born on the _______________ of December?"
2;912;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Choose the correct answer: "My friend is German. She was born in __________."
2;913;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Choose the best answer: "People who are born in Greece are __________."
2;914;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Choose the correct alternative: "Sushi and sashimi are __________ food."
2;915;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Choose the best alternative: "My mother was born in Turkey. She's __________."
2;916;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Complete the sentence: "My brother and I were born in Italy. We are __________."
2;917;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Complete the question: "Does your train leave at _______________ (4:30)?"
2;918;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Choose the best answer: "You're always late! It's already _______________ (10:15)!"
2;919;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Complete the sentence: "A person who drives a taxicab is a ________________."
2;920;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Choose the correct answer: "Mary works at a store selling clothes. She is a __________."
2;921;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Choose the correct alternative: "My nephew was born on the __________ of August."
2;922;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Complete the sentence: "Every year we celebrate our anniversary on the __________ of June."
2;923;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Choose the correct answer: "Classes begin on the __________ of February."
2;924;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Choose the correct alternative: "Adam is from Sweden. He is __________."
2;925;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Complete the sentence: "People say Swiss chocolate is the best in the world. It comes from __________."
2;926;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Choose the correct answer: "People who make bread are __________."
2;927;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Choose the correct alternative: "My aunt paints pictures. She is a __________."
2;928;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Complete the sentence: "Sarah plays the piano for the national orchestra. She is a __________."
2;929;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Choose the correct answer: "My cousin takes care of sick and injured animals. He is a ___________."
2;930;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Choose the correct alternative: "People who drive buses are _______________."
2;931;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Complete the sentence: "People who assist passengers in airplanes are _______________."
2;932;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Choose the correct answer: "_______________ work at police stations."
2;933;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Choose the best answer: "The __________ came by earlier this morning and left this letter for you."
2;934;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Choose the correct alternative: "I need to hire a few __________ to help me build my house."
2;935;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Choose the best alternative: "This building was designed by a very famous __________."
2;936;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Fill in the gap with the correct answer: "Einstein was one of the greatest __________ of all times."
2;937;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Fill in the gap with the correct alternative: "She's a __________. She cuts my hair."
2;938;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Fill in the gap with the best alternative: "_______________ fly airplanes."
2;939;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Choose the correct alternative: "She was born in nineteen eighty (__________)".
2;940;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Complete the sentence: "My office is on the __________ floor".
2;941;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Complete the sentence: "Rome __________ the capital of Italy."
2;942;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Choose the correct alternative: "My brother works in a restaurant. He's a very good __________." 
2;943;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Complete the sentence: "Ted always comes home covered in paint because he is a __________."
2;944;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Choose the correct alternative: "My sister loves kids, so she became a kindergarten __________."
2;945;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Choose the correct alternative: "Julie knows the Constitution very well because she is a __________."
2;946;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Complete the sentence: "The meeting will be held on the __________ of October."
2;947;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Complete the dialogue:xptoAdam: "When is Amanda's birthday?"xptoPeter: "It's on the __________ of July."
2;948;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Choose the correct alternative: "Hurry up! You are going to be late for the __________ time this week!"
2;949;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Choose the correct answer: "Lincoln was the __________ president of the United States."
2;950;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Complete the question: "Who was the __________ president of the United States?"
2;951;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Choose the correct answer: "It's 6:45."
2;952;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Choose the correct alternative: "It's a quarter to two."
2;953;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Choose the correct answer: "It's 11:15"
2;954;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Choose the correct alternative: "It's half past twelve."
2;955;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Complete the dialogue:xptoAimee: "What time did she say she would be here?"xptoSarah: "At a quarter __________ three."
2;956;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Complete the sentence: "Luk is from Switzerland. He is __________."
2;957;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Choose the correct answer: "Matt is American, but his parents are from France. They are __________."
2;958;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Choose the correct alternative: "Sally is from Canada. She's __________."
2;959;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Complete the dialogue:xptoAnn: "Where is Carlos from?"xptoTom: "He was born in Brazil, so he is __________."
2;960;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Complete the sentence: "Juan is from Mexico. He is __________."
2;961;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;How do you call someone who designs buildings?
2;962;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;How do you call a woman who works serving tables?
2;963;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;The day after Monday is __________.
2;964;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;January 3 is the __________ day of the year.
2;965;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Complete the sentence: "I love my city, especially _______________ the summer."
2;966;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Complete the sentence: "Today is Wednesday, tomorrow is __________."
2;967;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Choose the correct alternative: "July comes before __________."
2;968;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Complete the sequence: Ninety-seven, ninety-eight, ninety-nine....
2;969;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Choose the correct answer: "My daughter was born on the __________ of December."
2;970;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Choose the correct alternative: "Summer starts on the _______________ of December."
2;971;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Complete the sentence: "Peter's birthday is on the __________ of January."
2;972;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Complete the question: "Is Jennifer a __________? I always see her at the local school."
2;973;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Choose the correct answer: "People who act in movies are __________."
2;974;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Choose the correct alternative: "People who serve meals in restaurants are __________."
2;975;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Complete the sentence: "People who cook meals in restaurants are __________."
2;976;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Choose the correct answer: "My father plans and designs houses. He is an __________."
2;977;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Choose the correct alternative: "A person who grows vegetables is a __________."
2;978;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Choose the incorrect alternative: "I work for a hospital. I'm a __________."
2;979;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Choose the correct alternative: The __________ repaired my car."
2;980;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Complete the dialogue: xptoMark: "What time is it?" (7:10)xptoJohn: "It's ten __________ seven."
2;981;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Complete the sentence: "Are you __________ or __________?"
2;982;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Complete the sentence: "My brother designs websites. He's a __________."
2;983;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Choose the correct alternative: "I have a toothache, I think I'm going to call my __________."
2;984;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Choose the correct alternative: "My __________ is excellent. He takes very good care of my plants."
2;985;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;The fifth month of the year is __________. 
2;986;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;__________ is the day before Friday.
2;987;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;The nationality of someone from the Netherlands is __________.
2;988;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;How do you spell this number? "5th". 
2;989;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Complete the sentence: "We are not Brazilian, I'm __________ and she's __________."
2;990;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Complete the dialogue:xptoKate: "What does your mother do?"xptoKelly: "She treats sick people at a hospital. She is a __________."
2;991;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Complete the sentence: "I'm sorry, we're closed. We open _______________."
2;992;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;_______________ work together in a kitchen.
2;993;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Choose the correct answer: "She is going to take the train to Boston. It leaves at_______________ (6:45)."
2;994;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Choose the correct alternative: "The meeting begins at _______________ (6:30). Don't be late!"
2;995;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Complete the sentence: "Work starts at _______________ (8:30) every day."
2;996;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Fill in the gap with the best answer: "The __________ Stephen Hawking has changed his theory about black holes."
2;997;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Complete the dialogue:xptoTim: "What does your sister do?"xptoPeter: "She's a __________. She writes articles to the local newspaper."
2;998;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Choose the correct answer: "I'm going to the airport. My friend is going to arrive at _______________ (8:45)."
2;999;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Choose the correct alternative: "I woke up very early this morning. It was only _______________ (5:10)."
2;1000;Básico;Numbers, time, jobs, nationalities;Choose the best alternative: "I don't think you're late. It's only _______________ (1:55)."